<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="category_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_shops">Shops</string>
    <string name="category_taxis">Taxis</string>
    <string name="sights_statue_of_liberty_description">The Statue of Liberty is a colossal neoclassical sculpture on Liberty Island in New York Harbor in New York City, in the United States. The copper statue, a gift from the people of France to the people of the United States, was designed by French sculptor Frédéric Auguste Bartholdi and built by Gustave Eiffel. The statue was dedicated on October 28, 1886.</string>
    <string name="sights_central_park_description">Central Park is an urban park in Manhattan, New York City. It is located between the Upper West Side and Upper East Side, roughly bounded by Fifth Avenue on the east, Central Park West (Eighth Avenue) on the west, Central Park South (59th Street) on the south, and Central Park North (110th Street) on the north. Central Park is the most visited urban park in the United States, with 40 million visitors in 2013, and one of the most filmed locations in the world.</string>
    <string name="sights_empire_state_building_description">The Empire State Building is a 102-story Art Deco skyscraper in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. Designed by Shreve, Lamb &amp; Harmon and completed in 1931, the building has a roof height of 1,250 feet and stands a total of 1,454 feet tall, including its antenna. Its name is derived from "Empire State", the nickname of New York. As of 2017 the building is the 5th-tallest completed skyscraper in the United States and the 28th-tallest in the world. It is also the 6th-tallest freestanding structure in the Americas.</string>
    <string name="sights_times_square_description">Times Square is a major commercial intersection, tourist destination, entertainment center and neighborhood in the Midtown Manhattan section of New York City at the junction of Broadway and Seventh Avenue. It stretches from West 42nd to West 47th Streets. Brightly adorned with billboards and advertisements, Times Square is sometimes referred to as "The Crossroads of the World", "The Center of the Universe", "the heart of The Great White Way", and the "heart of the world". One of the world's busiest pedestrian areas, it is also the hub of the Broadway Theater District and a major center of the world's entertainment industry.</string>
    <string name="restaurants_jing_fong_description">Chinatown may be sprinkled with dim sum depots but this palace of Chinese delights is an essential stop, particularly for long brunches. Ascend the escalator to the upper floor and let the massive dining room unfold before your eyes. Roving carts, pushed by friendly diminutive ladies, are crammed with pork buns, shrimp dumplings, boiled chicken feet, and egg custards, among other delicious dim sum components. Point to whatever looks good and commence the feast. Sharing a large circular table with other diners is part of the fun experience here.</string>
    <string name="restaurants_katz_deli_description">In the early 1900s, the Lower East Side was home to a thriving eastern European Jewish community, and dozens of kosher delis. Today only a few remain, and Katz (opened in 1888) is the best. You may recognise it from the \'I\'ll have what she\'s having scene\' in When Harry Met Sally. The ordering process is a bit different: after you've been handed a ticket, place your order at the counter, indulge in superlative deli fare, and pay at the end with your ticket. Just don't lose that slip of paper or you'll pay a princely sum for the error.</string>
    <string name="restaurants_wildair_description">Wildair and its more formal sister restaurant next door, Contra, have infused some serious culinary cred to the bar-laden Lower East Side. And we have the two hot chefs – Fabián von Hauske and Jeremiah Stone – to thank for that. Perch yourself on a stool at a high communal table and peruse the wine list, heavy on the natural variety, while grazing on horseradish-spiked beef tartare, scallop crudo, and nduja and head-cheese toast. Or splurge on the fork-tender Wagyu steak for two. The bread and butter in itself is remarkable.</string>
    <string name="restaurants_balthazar_description">This beloved Big Apple culinary institution is the flagship eatery of prolific British-born restaurateur Keith McNally. It\'s like a small slice of Paris in SoHo: enter through the curtained doorway and find yourself in a gold-lit space with high ceilings and mirrored walls. The classic bistro options include oysters, steak frites, and a good burger. The raw bar is superb, as is the wine list. They do a great breakfast, and have a bakery, too, if you want to avoid the table hustle and grab a Parisian-quality baguette to go. Book well in advance.</string>
    <string name="shops_bloomingdales_description">Plow through the Bway, the aptly named, crowded main-floor arcade that feels like Times Square on Saturday, and hit the second floor for trendy, well-priced American brands. Bloomingdale\'s also carries all the requisite big-name designer labels and houses an extensive selection of lingerie. The Soho location caters to a younger, hipper crowd.</string>
    <string name="shops_barneys_description">Anyone worth her Manolos will tell you that Barneys’s Madison Avenue flagship is the final word in edgy designer fashion. The lower floors house sophisticated, expensive items like Prada suits; in the upstairs Co-op department, you’ll find rag &amp; bone jeans, Alexander Wang dresses, and oversize Helmut Lang tees.</string>
    <string name="shops_century21_description">The home of department-store designer leftovers that are at least—and often far more than—40 percent off. You’ll find everything from Hanes to Helmut Lang for men and women. The linen-department deals are even more incredible.</string>
    <string name="shops_apple_store_description">The two-story space boasts a showstopping glass staircase and a translucent walkway that glimmers in the sunshine flooding in from skylights. Test-drive everything in sight (iPads, MacBooks, software), play stump-the-tech-experts at the Genius Bar upstairs, or sit in on the free daily instructional seminars.</string>
    <string name="taxis_oncabs_description">OnCabs is the ride booking app to go with when you need to pre-book a ride in NYC. Whether you are in New York City for the weekend or live in New York City, OnCabs is the best Car Provider in town. We have Local, Trusted Taxis, Executive Cars, SUVs, Airport Shuttles and a lot more on our radar. We offer a state of the art ride booking platform that lets you book a car whenever you need to catch a quick ride, are planning a perfect business trip or just a family visit.</string>
    <string name="taxis_dial_7_cabs_description">Affordable and quick taxi and limo rides 24/7.</string>
</resources>
